In this video, we're going to talk about Coercions which is a feature of type
在这段视频中，我们将讨论强制，这是一种类型的特征
systems that appears in many languages and we will be looking specifically how
以多种语言显示的系统，我们将具体了解
coercions are done in Java. Java allows primitive types to be coerced in certain
强制是在Java中完成的。Java允许在某些情况下强制原语类型
context. And, coerced means converted from one type to another. So here's an example,
上下文。而且，被胁迫的意思是从一种类型转换成另一种类型。这里有一个例子，
lets take the expression one + 2.0 and the difficulty with this expression is that
让我们以表达式1+2.0为例，该表达式的困难在于
the, the one here is, is an integer and the 2.0 is a floating point number. And
这里的是一个整数，2.0是一个浮点数。和
there is no way to add an int to a float directly. We either have to convert the
无法将int直接添加到浮点数。我们要么必须将
integer to a float and then do the add as floating point numbers or convert the
整数转换为浮点数，然后以浮点数形式进行加法运算，或者将
floating point number to an integer and then do the addition as integer addition.
将浮点数转换为整数，然后将其作为整数加法进行加法。
So they have to be converted to a common representation, before we can actually do
因此，我们必须先将它们转换为通用的表示形式，然后才能真正做到这一点
the operation. And the normal thing to do, and the thing that Java does, is to
手术。通常要做的事情，也就是Java所做的事情，是
convert the integer to the floating point number 1.0. Now, a coercion the right way
将整数转换为浮点数1.0。现在，以正确的方式进行胁迫
I think, to think of coercions is they're really just primitive functions that the
我认为，考虑到强制，它们实际上只是原始函数，
compiler inserts for you. So it's like, you left out a function call and the
编译器会为您插入。所以这就像，你省略了一个函数调用，而
compiler notices that and puts it in. So, in this particular example, what would be
编译器注意到这一点并将其放入。那么，在这个特定的例子中，会是什么呢
the function call? Well, there, we can think of there being a primitive function
函数调用？好的，在那里，我们可以想象有一个原始函数
that converts integers to floating point numbers in the obvious way. And so really
它以显而易见的方式将整数转换为浮点数。所以真的
this expression here gets converted to the expression into float applied to the
此表达式在此处转换为表达式，转换为应用于
number one plus 2.0. All right. So coercions are probably best thought of as
一号加2.0号。好的。所以胁迫可能最好被认为是
a convenience for you, the programmer to let you avoid having to write some
对您来说很方便，程序员可以让您不必编写一些
function calls. And, so where it is obvious that a type conversion is going on
函数调用。因此，在很明显的情况下，类型转换正在进行
the compiler can insert the function that performs that type conversion for you. And
编译器可以插入执行该类型转换的函数。和
most languages really have extensive coercions so the conversions are very,
大多数语言确实有广泛的强制，所以转换非常，
very common particularly between numeric types and so this is not just Java. This
非常常见，尤其是在数值类型之间，因此这不仅仅是Java。这
is really many different programming languages of all styles that have lots of
实际上是各种风格的许多不同的编程语言，它们都有很多
differe nt kinds of coercions. Now, Java in particular distinguishes two kinds of
不同种类的胁迫。现在，Java特别区分了两种
coercions and casts. You have widening coercions and these will always succeed.
胁迫和施法。你有不断扩大的胁迫，这些总是会成功的。
Alright, so that means that Java will always put them in and there will never be
好的，这意味着Java总是会把它们放进去，而且永远不会有
any complaining from the compiler or the runtime system about them and we already
编译器或运行时系统对它们的任何抱怨，我们已经
saw one of those, so the conversion from int to float is an example of a widening
我看到了其中的一个，所以从int到Float的转换就是一个扩展的例子
cast. Now, narrowing casts may fail if the data can't be converted to the desired
演员阵容。现在，如果无法将数据转换为所需数据，则缩小转换可能会失败
type. So in particular, float to int well, this will work fine. Something like 2.0
键入。所以，特别是浮点到整数，这会很好地工作。大约是2.0版
can be converted in obvious way to two but if you're converting something that
可以明显地转换为2，但是如果您要转换的东西
doesn't have an integer representation something say like 2.5 you know, there's a
没有整数表示，比如2.5，你知道，有一个
question of what we should do here. Okay, and for such narrowing casts, where there
我们应该在这里做什么的问题。好的，对于这样缩小的演员阵容，哪里有
isn't a, a clear mapping, whether we should go or, you know or whether we
不是一个清晰的地图，我们是应该去，还是你知道，或者我们
should try here or round up, or whatever then Java will actually complain and not
应该在这里尝试或四舍五入或其他任何方式，那么Java实际上会抱怨，而不是
let you do it. Okay perhaps for better example of the kind of narrowing cast
让你来做吧。好的，也许更好的例子是缩小铸型
that's that Java will complain about is something like a down cast. So if I have
这就是Java会抱怨的类似于向下转换的东西。所以如果我有
two classes A and B. And B is a subtype of A and then I have something of type A.
两个A类和B类，B是A的一个子类型，然后我有一些A类型的东西。
Well, I can cast it to B. I can say, let's say I have X which is a type A and then I
嗯，我可以把它转换成B。我可以说，比方说我有X，它是A型的，然后我
can have an expression where I try to convert x to a B object. So here I have a
可以有一个表达式，其中我尝试将x转换为B对象。所以在这里我有一个
cast, I've indicated that I want to treat this expression x as a B object and this
强制转换时，我已经表示要将此表达式x视为B对象，而这
will type check, okay. So the, the compiler will let this through since B is
我会检查打字，好的。所以，编译器会让它通过，因为B是
subtype of A. But at run time, it's actually going to check whether x is
子类型A。但在运行时，它实际上将检查x是否为
actually a B object and if it's not you're going to get an exception. So this can
实际上是一个B对象，如果不是，你会得到一个异常。所以这个可以
fail at run time if the object thatt x actually holds at the point of the cast is
如果t x在强制转换时实际持有的对象是
not a B object. So the rule in Java is that narrowing cast must be explicit. You
不是B对象。因此，Java中的规则是缩小类型转换必须是显式的。你
have to put the function in yourself. You have to put in the typecase in the code so
必须把这个功能放在你自己身上。您必须在代码中输入类型大小写，所以
that it's obvious that you really want to do it, but widening casts in coercions can
很明显你真的很想这么做，但是扩大强制投射范围可以
be implicit, so it's alright. If you're widening, if you're either promoting to a
要含蓄，所以没关系。如果你在加宽，如果你要升职到
super type or you are converting between initial type where it's clear that the,
超级类型或您正在初始类型之间进行转换，
one type embeds in the other then those can be filled in for you by the compiler.
一种类型嵌入到另一种类型中，然后编译器可以为您填充这些类型。
And here's a little Java trivia question. So it turns out that there is one type in
这里有一个关于Java的小问题。所以结果是有一种类型在
Java for which there are no coercions or casts defined. Okay so there are no
没有为其定义强制或强制转换的Java。好的，所以没有
implicit conversions or even explicit conversions from that type to any other
隐式转换，甚至从该类型到任何其他类型的显式转换
type. And the answer to the question, which is the only one, is bool. Okay so
键入。而这个问题的答案，也是唯一的一个，是布尔式的。好的，那么
only the type boolean has no conercions or casts to another type. Now personally, I'm
只有该类型的布尔值没有公差或强制转换为另一个类型。现在就我个人而言，我是
not a big fan of coercions. I think that it's clearly a convenience for
我不太喜欢强迫行为。我认为这显然是一种便利，
programmers, it's clearly something that is widely accepted as being necessary in
程序员，这显然是一件被广泛接受为必要的事情
programming languages because casts, implicit casts and conversions are so
编程语言，因为强制转换、隐式强制转换和转换都是如此
ubiquitous but I do think that it tends to lead to programs that have behavior that's
无处不在，但我确实认为它倾向于导致程序具有这样的行为
different from what the programmer probably expected. And, here's a good
与程序员可能预期的不同。还有，这里有一个很好的
example from the language PL/1, which recalls stood for Programming Language one
PL/1语言中的例子，该语言RECALL代表编程语言One
designed by IBM in the 1960s. And had many, many features in it so we've talked
由IBM在20世纪60年代设计。有很多，很多功能，所以我们讨论了
about PL/1 a few times in this class. And one thing that PL/1 had was very extensive
在这节课上讲了几遍PL/1。PL/1有一件事是非常广泛的
cast and coercions and this could lead us to some surprising behaviors. So here's an
演员阵容和胁迫，这可能会导致一些令人惊讶的行为。所以这里有一个
example we have a, A, B, and C are strings of three characters so it's important to
例如，a、A、B和C是三个字符的字符串，因此重要的是
know here that the length three is part of the type. So B is string '123' C is '456'
这里要知道，长度三是字型的一部分。所以B是字符串‘123’，C是‘456’
and then A is going to be B + c and the question is what is A? And, and you
然后A就是B+c，问题是A是什么？还有，还有你
probably won't guess, so let me show you what I think is the right answer. So first
可能猜不出来，所以让我告诉你我认为正确的答案是什么。所以首先
of all the question is what happens with this + operation here? Well, so that is
所有的问题是，这里的这个+操作会发生什么？嗯，那就是
going to be interpreted as an integer + so B and C are both going to be cast to
将被解释为整数+所以B和C都将被强制转换为
integers and the, and this will be done as a integer arithmetic. So B will get
整数和，这将作为整数算术来完成。所以B会得到
converted to the number 123. C will get conver ted to the number 456, okay? And
已转换为数字123。C会把泰德转到456号，好吗？和
then we'll add them and we'll get out the number 579. Okay, so the result of this
然后我们把它们相加，我们就会得到数字579。好的，那么这件事的结果是
expression is 579 but A is also a string of three characters so this has to be cast
表达式为579，但A也是三个字符的字符串，因此必须强制转换
back to a string. Now, it turns out that this cast happens in two steps. First
回到一根弦上。现在，事实证明，这个演员阵容分两个步骤进行。第一
this, this number here is cast to a string of the default length, okay. And the
这个，这里这个数字是转换成一个默认长度的字符串，好的。以及
default length happens to be six so this is cast to a string looks like this.
默认长度恰好是6，因此它被转换为如下所示的字符串。
There's three blanks followed by 579. And then that string of six characters is
有三个空格，后面跟着579。然后这个六个字符的字符串是
converted to a string of three characters. And we just take the first three
转换为三个字符的字符串。我们只选前三个
characters and so we get out that, and so the answer is that this program stores a
字符，所以我们得到了这个结果，所以答案是这个程序存储了一个
string of three blanks in A. Which is probably not what was expected.
A中有三个空格的字符串，这可能不是预期的。